hey everybody welcome to this a one
english listening practice video you can
use this video to train your listening
and comprehension as I speak you ready
so today I'm going to talk about
language learning if you're watching
this video you're probably learning
English so I hope this is an interesting
topic for you language learning is hard
and if you learn a language you need to
spend a lot of time studying this is the
most important part of learning a
language time if you don't spend a lot
of time studying you won't learn English
language learning takes time I am a
language teacher but I'm also a language
learner I learn languages because it's
fun for me and I love talking to people
from other countries this is the best
part about learning another language you
can talk to many people and make new
friends I talked to people from many
different countries this is the fun part
of learning languages but language
learning is not easy sometimes I get sad
or frustrated when I can't understand
somebody I also get nervous when I talk
to people in other languages but that's
okay it's normal to get sad or
frustrated or nervous when you learn
another language this is normal
sometimes I make big mistakes when I am
speaking other languages I make mistakes
with grammar with vocabulary and with
pronunciation but this is normal
everybody makes mistakes when they speak
other languages if you don't make
mistakes
you won't improve to improve to get
better
you need to make mistakes you need to
talk you need to practice you need to
have fun so don't worry about your
mistakes have fun with English if you
don't have fun it is harder to learn
English
so here are
some tips to have fun with English
number one read books in English that
are interesting for you don't read
boring books find books that you like
for example if you like sports read
books in English about sports if you
like animals read books in English about
animals and if you like technology read
books in English about technology
I love fiction so I read fiction books
in other languages this helps me have
fun and learn tip number two watch
videos in English that are interesting
for you if you like fashion and clothes
watch YouTube videos about fashion in
English if you like cars watch YouTube
videos about cars in English it's
important to read and watch things that
are interesting for you okay tip number
three make friends who speak English and
make friends who are learning English I
know it's not easy to make friends but
it will help you learn and practice your
English find an English practice group
in your city you can look for an English
practice group on meetup.com
if you can practice your English with
friends it will help you a lot okay
we're finished for today leave a comment
and tell me why you are learning English
I'll see you next video